MoMA PS1 Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series I: Curatorial and Exhibition Records, (19682009)
  - Subseries I.A: General Files, (19702009)
    - Mexico City Artist Files: Miscellaneous Materials, 2002; Includes artwork images, ephemera, CVs, and other materials on artists. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 718, Folder I.A.3082*)
    - Mexico City Artist Files: Miscellaneous Materials, 2002; Includes artwork images, ephemera, CVs, and other materials on artists. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 206, Folder I.A.3083)
    - Mexico City Artist Files: Miscellaneous Materials, 2002; Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3084)
    - Mexico City Artist Files: Miscellaneous Materials, 2002; Artwork images and artist CVs with a top sheet labeled "artists in consideration." Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3085)
    - Mexico City: Kurimanzutto Materials, 2001; Artist biographies and materials from the Mexico City gallery. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3086)
    - Mexico City: Tour Packet Materials, 2002; Exhibition descriptions and images, press materials and news clippings. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): Press Release; News Clippings; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3087)
    - Mexico City: Catalogue Mockup, 2002; Image and text printouts folder and taped together, with some other materials. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3088)
    - Mexico City: Catalogue Mockup, 2002; Image and text printouts folder and taped together. Mexico City: An Exhibition about the Exchange Rates of Bodies and Values(June 30-September 10, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3089)
    - "2002 Architecture Project, Bill Massie", Mainly design visualizations. YAP (2002):Playa Urbana/Urban Beach by William E. Massie(June 30-September 1, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 207, Folder I.A.3090)
    - Urban Beach, 2002; Demolition schedule only. YAP (2002):Playa Urbana/Urban Beach by William E. Massie(June 30-September 1, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 208, Folder I.A.3091)
    - "Grennan and Sperandio", 9/29/2000; One piece of correspondence only. Modern Masters: Tales from the Pinnacle of Culture(May 19-June 23, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 208, Folder I.A.3092)
    - "Exhibition Working Files: Comic Book", 2001; Materials regarding the comic Modern Masters. Modern Masters: Tales from the Pinnacle of Culture(May 19-June 23, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 208, Folder I.A.3093)
    - "Modern Masters/Sperandio Proofs", 2002; Proof sheets of the comic produced for P.S. by DC Comics and artists Christopher Sperandio and Simmon Grennan. Modern Masters: Tales from the Pinnacle of Culture(May 19-June 23, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 208, Folder I.A.3094)
    - Tina Girouard, 2002; External proposal for a retrospective of the artist, with slides from her entire career (including one from an 1974 Clocktower exhibition, likely Discussions...) and other materials. Discussions: Works/Words(May 11-June 30, 1974): Installation Photographs (Box 208, Folder I.A.3095)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork Slides and CV, circa 2002; Slides and CVs of artists gathered and organized for an unknown purpose, but mixed in with press photographs from P.S. 1 exhibitions; artists include SHoP, Gordon Matta-Clark, Catherine Chalmers, John Curran, Sam Durant, Julian Laverdiere, Sam Miller, Sarah Sze, Felix Gonzalez-Torres, Lawrence Weiner, Los Carpinteros, and Andrea Zittel. YAP (2000):"Dunescape" by SHoP(July 2-September 2, 2000): Art and Event Photographs Los Carpinteros: Ciudad Transportable (Transportable City)(May 20-September 3, 2001): Art and Event Photographs (Box 208, Folder I.A.3096)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork Slides and CV, circa 2002; Slides and CVs of artists gathered and organized for an unknown purpose, with interleaved sheets listing the artist's name and country of origin; artists include Janet Cardiff, Javier Tellez, Angela Bulloch, Chris Cunningham, Liam Gillick, Monica Bonvicini, Noble Webster, Sam Taylor-Wood, Andreas Gursky, Peter Huyghe, Sylvie Blocher, Carsten Holler, and Olafur Eliasson. (Box 208, Folder I.A.3097)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork Slides and CV, circa 2002; Slides and CVs of artists gathered and organized for an unknown purpose, with interleaved sheets listing the artist's name and country of origin; artists include Miri Segal, Haluk Akakçe, Ilya Kabakov, Navin Rawanchaikul, Do-Ho Suh, Zwelethu Mthetwa, Santu Mofokeng, and Thomas Demand. (Box 208, Folder I.A.3098)
    - Artists Articles and News Clippings, circa 2002; Collected published material on the artists Thomas Demand, John Curran, and Sarah Sze. (Box 209, Folder I.A.3099)
    - Artist CVs, Articles, and News Clippings, circa 2000; Collected materials on the artists Dan Peterman, Lawrence Weiner, Sam Durant, John Miller, and others. (Box 209, Folder I.A.3100)
    - Artist Articles, and News Clippings, circa 2000; Collected materials on the artists John Miller, Julian Laverdiere, Gordon Matta-Clark, and others. (Box 209, Folder I.A.3101)
    - "Imodium Urban Relief Project" Project Binder, 2002; Unrealized port-o-potty themed exhibition sponsored by Ruder Finn Public Relations on behalf of McNeil Pharmaceuticals and curated by PS1 staff. Includes artist proposals, budget, drafts of the call for submissions letter, and correspondence organizes by tabs. (Box 209, Folder I.A.3102)
    - "Imodium Urban Relief Project" Proposal, 2002; Proposal for the exhibition by artist Mick O'Shea. (Box 718, Folder I.A.3103*)
    - Al Held, 2002; Checklists with insurance valuations for works by Held, in both his solo exhibition and group show that year; with some correspondence. Painting Report, "Plane: The Essential of Painting"(June 30-September 30, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation Al Held: Recent Paintings(September 1-November 1, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 209, Folder I.A.3104)
    - Al Held Checklists, 2002; Al Held: Recent Paintings(September 1-November 1, 2002): Checklist (Box 209, Folder I.A.3105)
    - Building Structures: Contacts, 2002; Lists of artists and contact information. Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3106)
    - Building Structures: Proposal, 2002; One-page proposal for the exhibition. Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3107)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Ricci Albenda, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3108)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Steven Brower, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3109)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Francis Cape, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3110)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: E.V. Day, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 209, Folder I.A.3111)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Peter Garfield, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3112)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Wade Guyton, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3113)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Chris Hansen and Henricka Sonnenberg, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3114)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Rachel Harrison, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3115)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Sabine Hornig, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3116)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Ian Kiaer, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3117)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Chris Larson, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3118)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Pini Leibovich, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3119)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Euan McDonald, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3120)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Rob de Mar, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3121)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Rita McBride, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3122)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Roy McMakin, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3123)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Patrick Meagher, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3124)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Manfred Pernice, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3125)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Michael Phelan, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3126)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: John Powers, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3127)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Tobias Putrih, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3128)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Joe Scanlan, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3129)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Lara Schnitger, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3130)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Nancy Shaver, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3131)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Daniel Simnmons, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3132)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Cheyney Thompson, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3133)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Shirley Tse, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3134)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Alan Weiner, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3135)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Clara Williams, 2002; Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3136)
    - Building Structures Artist Files: Miscellaneous, 2002; Information on various artists. Building Structures(September 23, 2002-January 31, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3137)
    - Daniel Marzona Correspondence and Notes, 2002; Includes "Short Century Chronology" of African history and meeting minutes on Video Acts. (Box 210, Folder I.A.3138)
    - Arnold Mesches, 2002-2003; Correspondence, checklist, artwork images, and other materials concerning venues for touring the exhibition. Arnold Mesches: FBI Files(September 23, 2002-February 2, 2003): Checklist; Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 210, Folder I.A.3139)
    - Arnold Mesches, 2003; Miscellaneous notes. Arnold Mesches: FBI Files(September 23, 2002-February 2, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3140)
    - Arnold Mesches Artwork Images, 2002; 11.5" x 17" artwork reproductions. Arnold Mesches: FBI Files(September 23, 2002-February 2, 2003): Art and Event Photographs (Box 718, Folder I.A.3141*)
    - Arnold Mesches Travel Documents, 2002; Arnold Mesches: FBI Files(September 23, 2002-February 2, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3142)
    - Arnold Mesches, 2003; Includes artwork slides and checklist. Arnold Mesches: FBI Files(September 23, 2002-February 2, 2003): Checklist; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3143)
    - Kenny Scharf, 2002; General information on the artist, with some correspondence and images of large works and notes on the checklist. Kenny Scharf(October 14, 2001-January 13, 2002): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3144)
    - "Exhibition Working Files: Kramlich Collection", 2001; Small amount of information on the Kramlichs. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3145)
    - Exhibition Correspondence and Documents: Kramlich Collection, 2002; Notes on installation plans. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3146)
    - Kramlich Collection, 2002; Notes, lists of videos of performance art, preliminary checklists, budget and installation materials. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3147)
    - Video Acts Loan and Return Forms, 2002-2003; Loan forms with some shipping documents. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; Entire folder restricted. (Box 211, Folder I.A.3148)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: Catalogue Materials and Checklists, 2002-2003; Includes photocopies from the Video Acts catalogue and P.S. 1 newsletter from Fall 2002. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): Checklist; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 719, Folder I.A.3149*)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: General Material, 2002-2003; Includes contact information, exhibition proposal, budget, installation diagrams, meeting minutes, and correspondence. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): Checklist; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3150)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: Correspondence, 2002-2003; Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3151)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: Artist Files, 2002-2003; Includes biographies, correspondence, installation diagrams, background information, and video stills organized by artist. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 211, Folder I.A.3152)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: Artist Files, 2002-2003; Includes biographies, correspondence, installation diagrams, background information, and video stills organized by artist. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3153)
    - Video Acts Exhibition Binder: Touring Exhibition Press and Correspondence, 2002-2003; Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): Checklist; Press Release; Installation Photographs; Printed Ephemera; News Clippings; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3154)
    - Video Acts: Notes, Proposals, and Readings, 2002; Includes draft project descriptions, with some notes and web articles. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3155)
    - Video Acts: "Kramlich Catalogue Electric Arts Intermix (EAI) Images Part I", 2002; Database printouts of thumbnails of video works and directories of image files. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3156)
    - Video Acts: "Kramlich Catalogue Electric Arts Intermix (EAI) Images Part II", 2002; Database printouts of thumbnails of video works and directories of image files. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3157)
    - Video Acts: "Kramlich Collection Lists", 2002; Various artwork lists and draft checklists. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3158)
    - Video Acts: Minutes and Correspondence, 2002; Meeting minutes concerning the exhibition from February through May. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 212, Folder I.A.3159)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: A, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, much of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists Doug Aitken, Vito Acconci, Darren Almond, Eleanor Antin, and Michael Auder. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3160)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: A-N, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, most of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists Marina Abramovic and Ulay, Eija-Liisa Ahtila, Peggy Ahwesh, Alex Bag, Phyllis Baldino, Pierre Bismuth, Seoungho Cho, Cheryl Donegan, Pierre Huyghe, Miranda July, Sylvie Lalibert, Mark Lewis, Sharon Lockhart, and Kristin Lucas, Sarah Morris, Nic Nicosia, Sam Taylor-Wood, and Gillian Wearing. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3161)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: B-F, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, most of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists John Baldessari, Matthew Barney, Stephen Beck, Sadie Benning, Joseph Beuys, Dara Birnbaum, Rebecca Bollinger, Chris Burden, Peter Campus, Larry Clark, Stan Douglas, Valie Export, and Peter Fischli and David Weiss. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3162)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: G-H, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, most of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists Gilbert and George, Douglas Gordon, Dan Graham, Rodney Graham, Gary Hill, and Nancy Holt. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3163)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: J-P, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, most of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists Joan Jonas, Mike Kelley, Shigeko Kubota, Chris Marker, Paul McCarthy, "Paul McCarthy and Mike Kelley," Steve McQueen, Mariko Mori, Bruce Nauman, Tony Oursler, Nam Jun Paik, Chloe Peine, and Raymond Pettibon. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3164)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: P-Y, 2002; Artist biographies, artwork descriptions, with some articles and other materials, most of the material printed from web sites and from the Electric Arts Intermix online database, on the artists Pipilotti Rist, Martha Rosler, Alan Ruppersberg, Bill Viola, William Wegman, Robert Wilson, Hannah Wilke, Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, and Young and Restless. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 213, Folder I.A.3165)
    - Video Acts Artist Files: Alex Pearlstein, 2002; Artist biography, video stills, and VHS cassette. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 214, Folder I.A.3166)
    - Video Acts: "Relevant Exhibitions", 2002; Internet printouts on related exhibitions. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 214, Folder I.A.3167)
    - Video Acts: "Kramlich", 2002; Notes, partial and draft checklists and floor plan sketches, with other materials. Video Acts: Single Channel Video Works from the Collections of Pamela and Richard Kramlich and New Art Trust(November 10, 2002-April 13, 2003): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 214, Folder I.A.3168)